https://www.bgcb.org/privacy-policy

Collection of Information
Boys & Girls Clubs of Boston (BGCB) respects your privacy, and will not collect any identifying or personal information about you except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information BGCB collects online through this site electronically, and manually through other means. We collect two kinds of information:  general usage data through the website, which is not individually identifiable, and individually identifiable information.
General Use Data
Our server automatically recognizes and collects the domain name of each visitor to our website. We collect information about visitors to the site, such as the number of visitors and donors, what pages they access, and the length of their visit. We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit the site or fill out forms, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows, Mac OS) and the domain name of the Internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Comcast). This information is used in aggregate form in order to manage our website and improve its content.
“Cookies” may be used in connection with the website. A cookie is a small amount of identifier data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. By using cookies, information is potentially collected without your express knowledge. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies but permit you to change the setting to refuse cookies or to be alerted when cookies are being sent. While refusal to accept cookies will not prevent the use of some portions of our site, other portions may not function properly without cookies.
Individually Identifiable Information
BGCB collects individually identifiable information about you when you choose to share information about yourself, for example, when you make a donation, request information or sign up for a program. This information may include, but is not limited to, your postal or e-mail address, your telephone number and your name.
We may request individually identifiable information in order to invite you to receive periodic e-mail updates about our work. We occasionally send out an email newsletter and direct mail communications to BGCB constituents to highlight news, information and opportunities available from BGCB. You can elect not to receive communications from us, either by contacting us at Info@bgcb.org or by noting your preference in response to communications from us.
We may request donor information when processing online or mailed-in donations you make to BGCB. When you donate to honor someone else, we do not use the information you give us about that person for any other purpose. We also may ask you for personal information at other times, such as when you ask a question or report a problem with our website. If you contact BGCB, we may keep a record of that session or correspondence, including a record of your e-mail address.
Use of Information
Individually identifiable information is used to provide you with information or to deliver the services you have requested and to provide you with additional services that we believe may be of interest to you. We use the information we collect to improve marketing and promotional efforts, to improve content, and to customize website services, content, and layout. BGCB also may use the information to inform you of new services, changes, or promotions.
Donor contact information is entered into our constituent database so that we can contact you in order to:
o    Supply you with information
o    Request voluntary time or monetary contributions to BGCB
o    Seek completion of voluntary surveys seeking feedback for quality and service improvement purposes.
If you provide your postal address, telephone number or e-mail address to us, you may receive periodic contacts from us. If you would like to change the way we contact you, you can let us know at Info@bgcb.org or 617-994-4700.
Sharing of Information
At times we may offer programs (e.g., contests or promotions) that are sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to participate in that activity. BGCB has no control over the third-party’s use of this information in this context.
We also occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf. We may share your personally identifiable information with these business partners and third parties, including e-commerce partners who provide us with this type of assistance. These may include, but are not limited to, credit card processing, fulfillment and shipping, database management, e-mail distribution, and website management. Such parties may use your personally identifiable information only for the specific purpose for which they are provided the information.
We do not trade or sell the personal information of donors.  We do not identify individuals as donors without their prior permission and we do not send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations.
In the unlikely event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, your personally identifiable information may be transferred to this acquiring entity.
Finally, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties in order to comply with law, law enforcement agencies, or to protect the safety or rights of BGCB or others.
Integrity and Security
In order to prevent unauthorized access and protect our users’ personal information, BGCB has implemented physical, electronic and administrative safeguards to secure the information we collect. For example, online donor contributions are processed using a secure server. This secure server software, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer), encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all the transactional data we collect is protected against unauthorized access with the use of digital certificates.
Notwithstanding our efforts to protect your information, no security system is perfect, and we cannot guarantee the absolute security of our databases, nor can BGCB guarantee that information you supply to us will not be intercepted while in transit to us over the Internet. BGCB employs commercially reasonable managerial and technical measures to help protect the security and integrity of the personal information it collects and records.
For areas of our website which require login, we ask that you help us protect against unauthorized access by keeping your password in a safe place and signing off when using a shared computer. We ask that you do everything that is reasonable to ensure the security of your personal information as well.
Privacy Practices of Other Sites
For your convenience, our website may contain links, or addresses, that you can click to open other useful sites where we do not control the content or privacy policy. We recommend that you carefully review the approach these sites take to your privacy before you use them or provide them with information.
We assume no liability for any unauthorized actions of third parties or accidental transmission errors that may disclose information about you, and BGCB is not responsible for these other sites’ privacy practices, which may be different from BGCB’s privacy practices.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998
BGCB is committed to complying fully with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. BGCB may collect certain personal information on a limited basis from or about children, including those under age 13, when the user submits it through our website (e.g., to register for camp or specific programs). Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to us. We strive not to collect any more personal information than reasonably necessary to enable children to participate in the activities we offer.
While we encourage children to visit our site and learn more about our programs, we recommend that parents approve and closely supervise the activity of their children at this and all other online sites. We urge children to check with their parents before entering information on any web site and we urge parents to discuss with their children restrictions regarding the online release of personal information to anyone they do not know.
Your Rights
Upon request, we will provide you with the contact information that we maintain about you. Further, we will respond to requests for updates or changes to your personal information. We recognize that you may wish to limit the ways in which we contact you. If you wish to restrict the internal and external sharing of your contact information, for example by excluding certain contact by telephone, email or postal mail, please let us know at Info@bgcb.org or 617-994-4700.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
BGCB may revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting. Please consult this Privacy Policy regularly.
DONATE
Follow:
Connect:
Find Your Club
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Boys & Girls Clubs of Boston | 200 High Street | 3rd Floor | Boston, MA 02110 | 617.994.4700 | info@bgcb.org
Privacy Policy
United Way
Interested Employer Partners
Name *Email *Phone Number *Company *Position *Program of interest *Best contact w/in your company *WebsiteSubmit
×
